<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CHIPcade Script - Arcade Chip Emulator</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/script/index.html</link>
    <description>With CHIPcade Script, you can program games for the CHIPcade system. It mixes high-level structure with low-level control — like a friendly assembly language that doesn’t bite.&#xA;Code Modules Every CHIPcade game has at least two modules:&#xA;init — runs once when the game starts update — runs every frame (60 FPS by default) You can add more modules using the ➕ button in the toolbar. For example, it’s common to add a Utilities module for reusable logic.</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/script/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Layers</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/script/layers/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/script/layers/index.html</guid>
      <description>CHIPcade features 8 graphical layers, managed by the Graphics Co-Processor. These are perfect for backgrounds, UI, parallax scrolling, and more.&#xA;You can access layers using:&#xA;layer[2].width = 800 layer[R2].height = 600 layer[2].mode = &#34;centered&#34; l[R2].visible = true Just like registers, you can reference them by index or indirectly through a register.&#xA;Default Behavior All layers default to the screen resolution Layers are not visible by default — set visible = true to show them Layers are automatically blended from bottom to top, with layer[0] at the back and layer[7] on top Layer Properties Each layer supports the following properties:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sprites</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/script/sprites/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/script/sprites/index.html</guid>
      <description>CHIPcade supports up to 255 hardware-accelerated sprites. You can access them via:&#xA;sprite[0].scale = 0.5 s[1].imageGroup = &#34;Bullet&#34; sprite[R2].layerIndex = 1 Just like layers and registers, sprite indices can be hardcoded or dynamically computed.&#xA;Sprites can also represent text via the text function.&#xA;Default Behavior Sprites are inactive by default — you must set active = true to make them visible By default, sprites are not assigned to any layer and are rendered on top of all layers Sprites can be animated, moved, rotated, and participate in collisions Sprite Properties Basic x, y Position of the sprite on screen (in pixels)</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>